<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on therealplato.com</title>
    <link>https://therealplato.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on therealplato.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://therealplato.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>#soberoctober day 2: out with the mold</title>
      <link>https://therealplato.github.io/posts/soberoctober02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://therealplato.github.io/posts/soberoctober02/</guid>
      <description>Keep catching myself reaching for my e-cig, locked far away. Bought seven types of gum to try instead. &amp;ldquo;5 Watermelon&amp;rdquo; package indicates a eating the whole pack results in a laxative effect, neat! Considered buying some nicotine-free ecig liquid but that feels like cheating&amp;hellip;
Today&amp;rsquo;s Achievements  Doused my moldy bedframe in sodium hydroxide Found and threw out a moldy spare pillow Yoga: for the first time in Downward Dog I touched my heels to the ground Set up Hugo and compiled these first posts from markdown  Arch, worth its own section&amp;hellip;  Got my brightness function keys working thanks to jmesmon/illum Learned how to close windows with awesome (default super-shift-c) Learned how to throw windows around workspaces (super-shift-2), switch workspaces, (super-2), reflow workspace (super-space) Learned why firefox was covering up all my other windows - I hit super-T instead of ctrl-T, making awesome &amp;ldquo;keep on Top&amp;rdquo;  Arch wishlist:  Show bandwidth use, wifi state, battery level in system tray Make my clock update DST automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#soberoctober day 1: challenge accepted</title>
      <link>https://therealplato.github.io/posts/soberoctober01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://therealplato.github.io/posts/soberoctober01/</guid>
      <description>Wut? Joe Rogan Experience #1007 introduced the Sober October challenge. I realized I couldn&amp;rsquo;t remember the last time I went a week without a beer. I&amp;rsquo;m certainly dependent on nicotine, I wonder if I am dependent on alcohol? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out.
Goal: Produce something useful each day this month instead of getting drunk and sucking at rocket league.
Rules: Caffiene is allowed.
Every other psychoactive substance is disallowed including nicotine and alcohol.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>